What happened, Hello friends, I am Piyush Patel from
Profits From It, I
heartily welcome you all. In today's Q3
result update, there has been an increase of ₹100. This
exercise has been done
in our channel for the last 15 days. How are you?
Now friend, the result for wala pure
is done.
This result of the mind has been discussed for how long.
In Wonderful Gold Improve,
we discussed Tata Elxsi Carnival.
Vijay Bhai Chaudhary ji has 124 group. After that,
we discussed these free Wipro
sir. On one side, bank
managers were discussed. Today, whose turn is it? The
results of the last company will be full. Enjoy 2020. Give some
information about today's cup and in the upcoming season,
we are going to discuss the results of the husband company every
day. So, there is a big
challenge for the students who will
repair these results. How will they do it?
Whatever results come every day, in what way will they scold them
and put pressure on you. How many
students of Hisar are doing jobs at some place or the other,
someone is doing business. It is clear that it is a
holiday.  But look at 10:30 pm we are all
meeting from very happy with
students we are more then we are going to
know the good results from these flights so the
results can tell us the trend so this
student and his team are leading the
doctor language from Pune health
welcome jute meet Yasmin Bank or Aggressor
General good sir thank you I mean bye you send a
smiley I think
everyone's results Mastani Wealth Creator this is the
result you need
save by Bhaiya I hope that for
how long have you been
collecting the group companies for years
market and Swaraj of disease we have three of our
students and the happy thing is that some
industry and today we will discuss and if we
talk about general insurance then these people will be there and
which has grown a lot and the
crowd of all the students has increased so they will
not be able to make even a home thank you tell this in such a good manner
today I was very happy to see their data
when I talked to them in the afternoon sir then all
three of them told me a common thing that
I said that this is your maximum
profit, the maximum life  What was the changing moment?
Everyone told me that the
3-hour meeting of the government on the Five Steps of Wealth Creation is the
most important because till date, in all the
courses that I have taught, I have been told by De
Villiers, we have never been told in this manner
that which step is right,
how will India become a Guru, there is a growing demand in the
industry, what are the systems in the demanding industry, so this
tremendous process, which is taught in this three-hour power
pack, is
not taught even in the PET course, so it was a
life-changing moment for all the students,
so I would like to thank Sir that due to the
information that is being given in 3 hours,
their journey has started
and the next course is tremendous, it is
not like that because everyone's pro-
Blutooth has increased tremendously, these days I
get that you have raised questions in my mind, this will definitely
give you curiosity, I feel that
I should do the five steps, a
lot of our energy of the entire year goes into this, this
cellent is present, behind every meeting there should be a
vision of Rs 2 lakh back.  It goes completely,
so it should go to every city. We used to
go to Lahore city twice with the entire team. It seems that even this much
money is invested and time
is requested. After this, there is unemployment here.
When the government balance is getting tremendous,
what do you think, how will we all
meet? What will we do in this? It will be
auspicious for everyone in the organization because
people's rallies are
different, they are not able to see each other day and night.
But if we talk about value, then there is no match
for the value. Diamond is diamond and what you get to
learn in 3 hours is really
life changing. If anyone is an honest
investor and wants to make good progress in the university or
change the future of his family, then he should not miss those three hours every
time because today we come to know
its value after 3 years.
So, if I tell you, even today I do
repetition of this thing every 15 days to a month because I am
getting its value. It is
amazing concept and in the dip, I keep crying.
Sir, it seems normal that please turn
off this setting when we go to the bank to pay the tax.
Your presence in big auditoriums,
Brahmins with big money and
no money, they used to do it in parties and the issue has been the
same meeting where mosquitoes bite,
like it was started in the last, the
students have started participating strongly, a
movement has started in these areas,
and because of this, sir, most of the
universals have become profitable, at
least, those who used to go to the wrong staff or
penny stocks, there was traction, that
of destruction has gone away, when thank you,
thank you, now what should I do, first of all, what will
we do on gas, so in today's
presentation, there will be about Shyam ji,
he is a student from Mela and he did a
degree in Electrical Engineering and is
working as an Assistant in Indian Standard Life Institute and
investing is his passion, so he is associated since 2018
and since then till today we talk, so you
first come, so the
question which comes, we
will talk about Alembic Sharma, let me tell you about Shyam ji,
his style of speaking is what
I like the most and very
simple language  Because I have
worked as a professor, first of all,
it will be told from their side today also, so we will
celebrate it with great enthusiasm, so come, welcome Hashim
Kirtania ji from Mohali, guide Rashid
Alvi Pharma,
thank you on this occasion, sir, you gave such a good
introduction, I liked it very much and first of all I would
like to thank Milan ji and full thanks to Profit From Its Peak for
organizing such a wonderful webinar that we are able to
share very good information even while being online, whatever I have learned to
you girl students, I am from a
financial background, as sir
told, so whatever I have learned, I can
share it with you people online and it is
possible that many people may get motivated by seeing me and may get into the
share market, hence I would like to
thank the Profit From
Its team a lot, now when I post my edition, friends, first of all
today we are going to
launch, friends, we will do a
complete edition of the pharmaceutical sector, there are
184 companies in it and today we are going to
discuss Olympic Pharma, first of all let us
look at the global scenario  If so,
why should I talk about global slavery, if we talk about this till 2019, then the
pharmaceutical market was
estimated to be 1.2 billion
dollars and if we
look at two Basit Kari ES, then this
pharmaceutical market will become 1.52,
1.6 clear dollars, meaning
growth is two to six percent, that
in the global market, now in some countries' global
market, if we see that US tax, if we do it like this, then in this way,
see how much is it by 2524, 605 means also 500, that
was 5 to 10 million dollars from Germany, there it will become 6535,
meaning three to six. The source of the question is if we
talk about Western Europe, then there are
top five countries in it, so how many are there,
six from Tehri, famous poet growth, if we
talk about Germany, there too it is 47 percent,
somehow if we look at UK, it
is four to seven percent, meaning it is a global market,
which we will see as developed countries there, so
now the process which is in between 36 percent,
now let us talk about other countries.  From other
countries, in the sense of where we live,
friends, live in India,
look at China, the
daily estimate made till 2019-24 was
five to eight percent protest
and what is the score of the Indian cricket team, friends, one of the growth,
friends, one is almost tomorrow spending and
growth, that is, those who will clarify that there will be
growth in this sector, that is, if this project is done then the
company is going to benefit, so there is a
need for a deeper percentage than art, so that
means where is the maximum growth happening,
friends, our country is more,
so when there will be protest, this pending will increase, then
what will happen in this tractor, friends,
all these companies will benefit, all the
good companies are here, let's
see now friends, which are the growth
inspectors, which animals, which
things are opposed to this tractor,
I have written 57 points here,
friends, you can see what is our
economic development here, friends, this is
rapid urbanization, this is the chapter, then
what is it, friends  F-18 which is improving
affordability in metropolitan and
city festivals are
coming up because people's income
is increasing and somewhere or the other facilities are increasing
so this is also increasing the third point is
friends increasing access to
modern medicine
what is happening to SSB towards modern medicine is one thing and the
fourth what is being seen friends the
lifestyle of food is rather lifestyle is changing the
pattern of Lakhan Lal Mission is
also changing
what will happen due to this change that there are new designs that you know
like more people are going towards fast food if they
eat fast food then they will get busy somewhere and if they go then they will
benefit the pharma sector and what else
awareness is also coming among the people in the garden so they are
going towards health care means health care so these are all the points due to which
we feel that there will be growth in this sector
and if we look at the sector Lalit then
tractor like we told that there are 184
companies in it then how much is the total market of
friends approximately 10,000 bodies  The
market cap is 10 lakh crores, so
in the market cap of 10 lakh people, Alembic Pharma's market share is
approximately 110.7
percent. So, one thing
we have to keep in mind is that it is a very big company,
but why are we discussing it here?
We have to keep in mind that we are discussing it because the
results of this company come first, so by
liking its results we
can conclude how our tractor is going to
perform, how is the work going to be done in this company that we have
invested in,
we will get a director for that.
Now take the sales and make it medium. The
sales of LMB Pharma is 2.7 percent, which
means that out of the total company, it is
approximately 2.7 percent, so this is a
lot of
trouble,
sorry sir, this will come in a little call. Okay, the
Lambi Pharma number is 1212.
In terms of trail, see the profit. If you look at the
profit, see
how much is its profit. Right now
Lambi Pharma has a profit of 808 crores.
Which are the most viewed major players? So Sun
Pharma and Vindu Pharma,
Cipla, Lupin,
all these companies have only one.
Hello friends, return home page up equity
return of difficulty,
technology one or two, the above
accused theft of return paper,
what is turn on pay difficulty, how much did the
investor invest and
how much is he earning today, if you look at it then you will
see how much is happening here,
twenty one times, that means twenty
one times what is happening for the equity he invested, it is a
lot here, that means he is getting that much times return,
similarly look at the net profit
margin, so what is the net profit margin,
friends, see which one has the highest,
Divi's Lab has the highest net profit
margin, after that if you look at it then LMB
Pharma has a net profit margin of 17.4 percent
and till now it is more than ICL,
interest coverage ratio means how much is it
earning on interest, if you look at it then LMB
Pharma has 38.7, what does that mean
Do almost a date and here you will see that there is
an organization of date which is very much
that Divis Lab so wife slap day
three company in this sector so best
porn site which is on the left hand side the
form in the channel is almost get free
company how much is 38% it can pay
38 times the interest it has to pay
means it is a good company now let's
see the graduation valuation by the way
we have just seen its growth in this
see its price opposition it started from 3838 percent
so if you had invested one lakh rupees in it eight years ago
then it would have become
32 lakh rupees now that means if
you had invested 108 years ago then you would have got 32 lakh
rupees and if
we see how has been the dead sales growth of this company then we will
see the sales opposition squad
in the last 10 years in 2010 it was
1138 crores and today in 2019 it has become
4611 crores meaning there is old times increase and
this  Because in terms of profit, it has
grown by 15% every year. Similarly, if
you look at the profit, it was 40 crores in 2010,
whereas today it has become 800 crores, meaning
Shyam Singh. And in terms of profit and share,
how much has happened in the 35th
series? Similarly, look at the net profit
margin, which was only 3.5% in 2010, it has become
17% today.
Friends, there has been tremendous opposition at 17 points,
meaning it is able to maintain its margin.
And look at the reserves, it has been made excellent here too.
If you look here, the result in 2011 was 258 crores,
tell me what happened to God,
friends, here it is 3182 crores, meaning there has been
tremendous opposition. What will happen if the results increase, the
bills of the company will increase.
What do we do then, friends, we distance the quarterly results.
How was the
result? If we compare the result of 2019
quarter and 2020-21 quarter, then the
sales growth, friends, can be
seen here,
profit growth of more than 40 points.  It was 145 points
304 A pies grow from 1 43.75 and at the same time
we saw that our GDP data which came was
how much like this - 03 questions
GDP data came and here how much forty
verses
that I somewhere felt that in this
chapter our GDP is going to outperform our soil, we understood that in this chapter our
GDP is going to
outperform all, similarly let
us see the test one result of more six months, the other one
also had good growth, how much was the sales growth, in
27th the profit growth is 65
percent and how much is the GPS growth is 69
percent, similarly the latest
result of the ninth, we will compare the
result of 9 months in tub of 2020 and 21, you will see
how much the opposition is showing, then
from God you will see the profit is 59% and GPS
is 50%, so somewhere one more point is
left, so we will comment on the nine month results, let us proceed with
this, then we will see its
price.  If you can estimate
how much it will be, then consider this backward value,
how much will it be? 266 166 rupees
is forward GPS, according to this,
how much does the intrinsic value come out, friends,
its internal milk comes to 1124 rupees, so if it is the correct
value or not, then our cold man
quality is, so we try to see through the chart what kind of
dip has happened in it, so
look, on one side it will be visible here,
this index which is Nifty Pharma,
what is it doing, till now it has
not given breakout to the sector, which is Pharma
of India, it has not given breakout,
this means friends, like there are 184 companies, most of the
companies will not be good, some
companies are good and the
companies below there will not have good profit and margin,
so what is it, this chapter is not
performing well, it is
not showing any problem or promise, but among these there are some
companies which will work for the sector as well as for the
soil and we will also work for the GDP
and we will do this, like see here,
Lambi Sharma, which we developed Amit, so we will
understand through the chart also, so for the last
five years, there has been no such performance in it.  Guru was not there, a
range was going on, just this year the explanation has
given the record in it, so somewhere
we are seeing this range, you can red
light, so this here between 700 to 800,
somewhere between 9 here,
you can have a good price, I
can buy milk at the lower level, as low as it will be available, so friends, I would
also like to give you a disclosure, friends, I do
not have any holding in this company,
I have a holding in Divi's Lab in this sector, so if
someone wants to buy milk, then let's
see how much to buy, then there is
confusion, it is good, that the growth is good, that is,
in this company and in this sector too, it is
very good, as we have seen, the sales are
very good, the profit is very good, the
margin is good, it is almost gate free company,
so we should invest in a good company somewhere in this sector, if
you
want to invest in this company,
you can keep one to two percent of the total portfolio, but
disclosure, you should keep in mind that by me it does
not mean that you have to buy, you have to buy,
I can tell you my own  I have
folded in Divi's Lab that all
are the best companies, leader companies, we always submit
that you should stay with Reliance company, so
before taking it, you must consult your financial advisor,
this is
my opinion, so you can get it, thank you sir,
after that sir, let you have
a meeting brother, brother, let me speak this point differently,
practice, so all the people who have
heard the presentation of Hashim Bhai, first of all, the
direction is amazing, Ashish Bhai has a
strong command over Hindi and the project
presentation because it is
explained very well and you
told about the growth of the industry, whether the industry will grow or not,
which company is good, from all these things the
medico idea is clear that what should I take,
wonderful Ashim Bhai, but I
request you that if there will be a presentation of another company, then
before that,
write down all your queries, so that it does not happen that
now look at the second company and then
forget about the well-being of the first company, if you want, you can
write it in a note, you
can request my voice from now on, we will
also answer the presentation.
You will give feedback on this after that, so you
can put query message in send box, white
inauspicious one away, clear these people, okay,
tremendous presentation on loot loot do
take a profit
that today the world, our next presentation
expresses the intention and his from
Indore and he has registered on ICICI Lombard,
now I would
like to say two-three things about sister ji, when I was
talking to her, sister ji had
said that she has a desire to make profit
from the East, so her H.E. is less,
secondly she is a software engineer, B. Computer
education and that is her dream that according to
Flirty Ledger 14512 detail show wealth
creation, she has all these
learning things and in which she is very
tremendous, whose commanding nature is of this,
see in the presentation, so I will tell P Bank ji to
start the presentation,
such that ICICI Lombard
can be a tremendous company in the agro industry,
so the entire channel about this company,
what is the current situation, what to do next,
I will engineer that  I will come
Mr. Mahendra Shah,
thank you sir, thank you sir, after secretary, welcome
to Hello friends, I
welcome you all on behalf of Mansha Profit From Its A
and I am going to do an experiment, there is
a general insurance company, it is a
tractor company, its main pimples will be
discussed, so first of all let's
understand what is general insurance cover,
general insurance, whatever non-life
insurance thing is there, I cover all the general
insurance, like we have your car
and all sectors, car motor
insurance, that about the body, first of all let's
see, the setback junior
of 60 crore dishes crores and
we can also see that it is close to 1100 crores
and the profit is also close to 6000 crores
and about the numbers, first of all
unite and point is that
within our private insurance sector, it is the leader in the general insurance sector and
maintains the leader position,
if we take from the market, the
shift between private players is also very important
and in the overall industry,
we can see the biological chemical percent disgusting star mark,
school van, infant this  The company's turnover is 2.7
times, which is quite above the minimum set.
Now let us see
what is the certified growth in this industry. As we
can see, if we look at the GDP
penetration here, if we look at it
in GDP percentage, then this register is
1.5 percent and
if we look at India, till now it is 0.05
percent, so we can see that GDP penetration is
possible in India and as
we know, it has the world's largest
population, so insurance here is also quite
low. Now let us go a little
and see the
performance of the companies in the big industries.
If I say, if we look at the top ten
industries, if we look at the international
industries, then we can see that it is around Rs.
4.5 lakh crore, it does
not have anything to share. And
here, if we look at ICICI, then
it is around Rs. 1100 crore.
Berkshire Hathaway, which is one of the most famous companies of
our Mr. Mohan and mutual, it also belongs to this
tractor and I want to
put a point here.  I would like to say that
some Chinese companies have protested in the last 5 years in
complete detail against China, from
this letter
we can see the use potential of protest in the industries of all the developing and growing countries, so in India right now there is a lot of protest.  So, first of all let
us see
what are the vibrations of the power generation sectors in India, manufacturers industries,
so we look at general insurance
tractors, here CT running
central insurance is free and our
standalone health insurance, so we
call those companies which provide specifications and another one is
for industries and farming, it is
related to the public sector, here
now we will focus on our major sector, it belongs to it, so if I had seen that
like
general private sector, then we will
see its six, that is near about
fielder, it is alone
and is the market leader, when we discussed earlier
that from 2018 and now the major market share,
as we can see that the corporation has to go near the
market, sir, HDFC Agro, it is
covering more protein, now let us
discuss the license number, let us
see some history, as we
can see that from very low premium, the
revenue of the Prime Minister in fabric, the premium is growing, it is
growing on the income website also  If we
look here, we see a continuous
growth here, so where is this
2058 crore only, right now we have increased it
to 1100 crore, in profit
also we are taking, so this mystery is repeating,
the state from the second crore torch and right now
we are close to 1500 crore, let's
talk about a current affair, now let's talk about
current affairs, the point we are going to discuss is
courier, so in the video, for example, the
seal of our complete lotan screen was taken - wife in fact which and
as soon as we look at the profit, here
in this cross, the doctor became profit by 20%,
where is the major point behind this, there is also
a major shift in ICICI General Inspector, and it was
written in the text
that 30% tax payer change, which is
25% expression only and
as we can note here, continuously in the
last three quarters, right now in the ninth,
we do plus 4%, we are watching the video, pass
means we can do extra on this
This company will invest in lifetime sales and in
profit also we will invest in last time profit
so we can expect that we
can also invest in light. Let
us discuss the share
holding pattern of this company. We
can see its one percent to near about
promoter holding. Advection is the largest
holding, so 17 percent mutual
fund has 20% but if we look at the results then it seems to be
holding only about seven percent.
Now let us discuss the statement
traveling tips. What will we get by discussing central.
Our trick zones can also be
identified by looking at the sectors. We
can see that the rich person of this industry is
Vyara. Mode and third party insurance could
not stop sandwich and various
revenues. This is the mark and 22% revenue is
health. Now we can say that 75% of
travels is coming from 3 sectors. So we can discuss
one topic here. Wait a minute. So
we can see here as soon as the Motor
Industry Minister  There is a meter against the beads,
so here I will look at any business, as soon as there is a
boom in the hotel industry, then
we can see double growth in their business as well.
In the middle of this is health insurance,
here in a response we
can see that the premiums that they charge can be
under control, according to most of the government, ITI,
RDA, there has been a lot of
confusion, so
we will discuss some of the income fund companies,
now let us consider some estimates of this company,
look into the
history, where has it been,
in this company we can
expect serious growth in the coming time,
and if we mix it in, then after
taking oil from fifty thousand crores till now,
and the profit should be
around about three and a half thousand crores, from this, so
we will spend 15 minutes looking at its
entry price, which after this benefit we have to enterprise
from here, now
we will also do some fundamental business  Let's discuss.
Yes, if we look at the fundamental levels,
long term, this is golf. We can see that
we can keep its long-term target around 43 thousand.
In the short term, we can increase it by
10 percent. If
we want to look at the wine labels, we
can select that level around 300. We will have to have a
complete address in this industry
because this company will have to be at the forefront
because as we can see, there are
lifetime high sales and profits. So, I would like to
give a little information about this company. It belongs to the
Amar Singh sector and I
believe that it should be a complete area
because
it is a growing and emerging sector.
Now, we have growth potential, GDP growth
in India and penetration.
If we talk about portfolio location, then
here we should do this pocket 4%
portfolio. But still,
before investing, you will have to
take your three fundamentals and study them.
Take this mother, not on the table because I am also a
student, which is right for you, I am
learning and
I will come now and at the end of the presentation I
want to thank my team Vikas without any fear I don't be able to complain about the
presentation which includes Pav Bhaji Ravi Sthal and
our teacher Munimji and most of all our
guide central and guru to them I
can thank Satya of the
best friend thank you thank you sir ji
Lut
Hu is the wonderful man brother very very good
son very very good you have studied
and presented it well in this way
life and love your data Africa what
you have written about Naagin 3 seventh market
fans profit is well written, it is
immediately known how much
profit is there on how much sale is seen on the market, isn't it good, this
market that I think if there is a
market app of seventy thousand crores, that
means it will come in a bowl in the soil,
I will take the left channel Radhe-Radhe and
tell the people that I can also click on Mary's note and that
you
110 why mosque one then  This is Amar Singh
Industry and the Gular that we submit is
in the mature industry.
It was challenging because the data is
not available to dig deep. You had to go through
old annual reports,
red herring prospectuses and search a
lot of information.
Divine deficit and is one of its very good
ways. I would also like to tell the rest of the people
that this industry is
really a growing industry. As
I told in comparison, what is the condition of US and
what is the condition of China and
we are at least 10-50 times behind. So
our opposition potential is huge. So you
cannot ignore this inverter company at all. So thank you my dear sir, on
giving gems and great multibagger to all.
Back in the next presentation, sir,
ours is also by the name of Mr. Tarun Vijay. Tarun
Vijay is a
retired person from the Army. He retired this year
from the rank of Gadget One Officer in the Army
and for the last 4 years, he has been conducting
meetings in the product market.
Meaning and reading is government pension and
he has taken all the benefits in the family in the table,
meaning he had joined only four months ago, he has been
guitar percent button's energy
level and the dedication of the army is
reflected in his body as well, so I will
ask Tarun Vijay sir that the president should give
us a presentation on ITI today which will be
very helpful for many of our missions,
welcome Tarun C is there
and tell me
Jhal, thank you sir, thank you very much, so
friends, now I am converting that you,
good evening friend, thank you, thank you
sir, thank you sir, that whole soft fy09 rising
star only country on that
ITI belongs to IT consultancy and
software industry which comprises of
several complaints, belong
to you calling entries interested
preventing service blog
visitors every sector and most important key
dedicated justice growing wheat
flour present because we plate it
400 fit investor respect important see
Biscuit free water content trade demand
and water sector is this a centimeter key trend
improved tract is software
and computing technology is transfer
liquidity chakravarti block b
manufacturing energy automotive david
banking finance take this lineage office online
education for online vote through online
retail ki kamar medical care media
entertainment and lists and led on is
video customer expert tuesday tweet tweet
coming mode customer centric customer
satisfaction to work at most important
and share data edit explanation
important role automation and secure
process
meanwhile earth individual differences and not to meet in the
core processor transformations
taking place
which is distribution is your a
hello friends paste process par bring
more info kar more and more not present
government channels word pairs not only that
governments also taking initiatives
in times of india and writing services like this
post and company industry ki
technology david competition competition in
hindi subscribe channel  Channel
subscribe middle no of liquid subscribe karna hain
normal acid deposit in the
greeting below the tag is coming digital and
difficult is remind digital technology
area developed fastest growing in
revolt and big data analytics cloud
computing cyber security artificial
intelligence internet of things 3D
printing robotics election and in worship
bt has a
node wow interactive and see what is the
market cap se z
that avadhi par fasting market kya paise dat
of cent in the road and which is the leader is it is in this
sector ki kaam wanna to kiss her
a special offer anti eye and 1100 crore
party wear dresses and your profit in which is fitted to be able
to cigarette during declare
his approximate ring
1500 crore rupees ki hai
some deficiencies to communication officer position
net profit margin between that
indicates daily net profit generated a
percentage of revenue it has been able to
generate annual profit morning near 14%
vijay hotspot of the  In ltd tcs
report unleashed year which stands and
interest coverage ratio kidnapped in
multiple times it is his
percentage 90 which indicates digit
pin capacity offer complete now through water
pollution in this Light is dad ko lowest
printed tractor
jo hai woh aisi aur a very good ccr
exit date di and recovery date increased two
finance for clearing district companies
but basically date belongs to play list
diabetes and on account upon its nature important
factor to consider here easy
accused decreases in written update of equity
shares on calculated in multiple times it into it is just
accused hindi
sector
a letter written with spirit to speed up
equity and dignitaries chief accused complex
return on equity specific per cent of
lti-1 key
print after having seen the interactive
this time not to hay people global company it is a
global technology consulting
and digital solutions for legal updates
bell t-20 use jo rahe  Inheritance of the
perimeter meeting its products mission
public offering july 2016 and last year
quantity date 15x an operation a rs.32
country batao that blue with more than for
investment and important 368 comments
bills coating powder distance number
important dr the
voice of difficulties but not follow the
rules and regulations 135 key
speed reddy service mystery but
from this point complete detail officer service to
lines from diverse interests which are
included in this service insurance
energy kuwar kuwar retail pharmaceutical
hi-tech media entertainment print t-shirt key
sector 5 minute ruk post duty time when
a person will not dependency perform
550 225 song 2020
ki virwar taraf notification champion percentage
changes during this period the company has also been able to earn profit
five
times from present in 2018 schedule
for fifteen hundred par hoon duty se to
dogs  Significant is back please
friends that it is complete say you guru
interested by four three inches to call us
for this site question se daddy company is the
worst performer in revenue and
profits of planning department native
with curd train syndicate bank in nineteenth
addition ignore it 2016 and field
and profit is school ground in ascending
keys per cent in the speakers is
looting the growth rate of season profits
for this site and he has been estimated at the
current year ago leave and profit will
provide 1627 per cent sparing but word
doctor withdro 50% between taken 3 taken into
consideration wicket straight until pier after
it 2030 51 company is just able to generate on the
other hand western it on them hussain
problem do i will
not consider and hmm
why if important parameters like
share meeting set
a p promoter singh and turmeric four percent
servi  Company Ford Aspire for
investors 106 device wifi per cent
and detail share is six per near expense
increased by completing its and employee
benefits which a specific perfect
company is shopping independent country
concentrating his inspiration for the current
year it has been created strs videshi a
humko payment of fundamental elements to
complete the university jobs ki
technical director click on market
price of the companies have not even he
zindagi chart key counter and list on that
july 16th today after 67 years after it entered
into marriage between 22018 is
and animals ke peen 3150 life span of key
counter it hindi aaram hoga daily life
line hot in line 2021 from time it is
movie lekar rocket direction hogi is taraf
dandruff and made like times five points
from january 08
and interesting on ₹10 interested in doing it now
that guddu guddu 501 likes today  To
conclude I would like to mention that
companies are consistently painting exhibition
profits at a fast speed listing details
metal items only revenue advice items IT
profits and left my pride in the
next 3 years painted generating
revenue from Paytm app open phone
price rate of country more than 50
status
report quantum prince creation in
its benefits edison baby tandoori from near
this mountain F1 appendix-2 invest
in this point arrested in the department want
to 2% the portfolio amount chief
investment with its composition end of
my channel this thank you very much for your
question here and now it is open for
increase thanks sir that has happened
and thank you very much to you also Tarun ji
because divas world immigration and Ashim
bhai jo hai na toh me bhi aadmi hai his
presentation is very nice to listen to
and we have full confidence that Ashim bhai will
come no worries his data vaibhav  All the
best Mayank bhai, I think this is the
third presentation, this is a
very good presentation of this Improvising Shayari,
this was a video of Tarun bhai, but Tarun bhai did what the
Indian team did yesterday
in Australia, winner, I have heard that when some damn
good player took a few stitches to take a wicket,
so Arun bhai, your track
in your presentation has given us victory, that is the
value of pure, Sanjay, with his peace,
presented very well, I will do it wonderfully
and the data is very good, you are deceased, you were
sanctioned by Yasmin Bank Sir,
Tarun ji is an employee of Bhiwani station, I have
joined the classes and in so many clothes,
such a good dedication and neat and clean
presentation, absolutely professional level, all the
data that you have collected is praiseworthy, I
mean, being able to do so much in such a little time,
his army's deep list and
energy level is reflected in it,
Shubhendu
is Yasmin and successful, so what can we do,
we will have an effect against Ajwain fashion, I would like to
allot it to Sir, like
from the shore tomorrow  Sir, there will be tension in that Ashok
Sonkar from Upleta, Gujarat, so he has
WELL and ATS and Partha
ji is from Ranchi, so his HDFC AMC
will be all presentations, okay, so we should get
ready for it, tomorrow there is WON ABC and
Larsen & Toubro, https://right, okay,
theirs will also be there and their fans, all these
companies, whatever you are giving here, this is
better, our investors have it in the group,
yes sir, because all these are wealth
creators and do a proper multi-way or a
wonderful wonderful list including adults, peppers on
one end, oceans and
scientists,
your question officer, they say, the
lower area of ​​gentle request, darling,
separate tuition, please, okay, so
what will we do, whatever video will be uploaded,
so the video is already live, so
you won't get it right now, but tomorrow
you will get it in the presentation in the link of some video,
right, and similarly, in the rest of the
presentations, you will get it in the video,
all the presentations are there because all this is
made for you students,
which you should get and
I let me rate all the mode
that Arvind ji Ravindra ji is saying
what price target shoot me for anti
i 125 so a truly believe we have taken and
Harvinder ji is my very good friend, I have a
workshop in New Delhi, so I live at his house,
but he should tell Arvind ji what is the
target, so when it was stuck, I invited
Har Govind Soni, estimated
to growth of 3 percent for long term date
of birth target of classes, you should subscribe for this, if you
keep subscribing then it is
₹5000, the market is more than expected
because because of this, as Tarun ji told,
click on industrial automation, till now the
money has come from A countries, now slowly it will
also come from developing countries, expect
the cost of tube light of IT sector will increase, so we
can do more than this, but according to me, forget the
targets, money is strong,
I have no idea to book this,
Tarun,
thank you,
now half question, Acharya, very nice, various
levels, servicing, January  2017 Definitely,
you will get presentations of Prashna Music and all other good companies in the same way. Thank you
Doctor Hotel Desai thank you rent or
thank you Doctor from exact servicing
Capler Night Madam, it has not been put up yet
and we will put it up tomorrow if you check the video
then that link will appear Rakesh
yes brother Laddu ok nice presentation
thank you Rakesh ji and Rakesh request is the
king of the show how much percentage can be
invested in lti-1
that if I want to invest in IT sector,
I feel that I can
invest 12th of the best, then can you
tell me how much should I invest in which company.
In ID,
like this uniform guiding principle not more than
twenty percent pinch allocated to
protect my own interest that pra Justice
Govind Sector s Lord of demand and
expectation from this factor remains
hello how to best android world not
educated all the best person to any one company
Sector-23  Competition investors set
New Delhi fear of trying TCS Wipro
Sterlite shares and duster growing in
emerging sector which acid is not more than seven
percent invested TCS
that thanks that section mind with
recruitment one to per cent of the court should
you invest in lti-1
that whether absolutely correct bloody so keep in
mind that you can invest more money
TI good company can please the house
ok so next Ravi Goyal Dr Ravi
Arora ji told all of them Pankaj Pankaj Pankaj Rana
ji's company has a
potential to move forward listed
company TCS is that in every case
that shoulder as Tarun ji told you
in this under Infosys you have to decide quickly
Friday small company ok Ashok
ji gave you all or thank you Ashok Jain
Jain Kishan ji from which is used for
health education as I had kept that if you
say then very good Star Health will get it
and yes
sir if we Star Health  If we talk about it, then
this standalone health insurance sector
means it will come under the category, it does
not come under general insurance, so their business model is different
and as we can see that their hundred
percent is helpful, but near this number, there are
also motor fair and marine producers from
where the major value system is
coming from restored industries, so there will
not be that much interest from motor, yes, add it, now let's talk about
insurance,
like I have also included health insurance
in my bill, if we talk about
their skills, sales and mind, then there is a lot of
difference and their market share is also less in terms
of industry, so still
I think that it must have seen it moving at this number
because by maintaining leadership and being
plastic, due to which the company has told the market,
yes, how much market share does it have in insurance,
MP3, okay,
one thing is clear, the pressure of insurance
increases, no one can stop it,
in developed countries, more people increase their money,
but a little more and
now we will also add a little more to this,
looking at the data, it seems that such a number has a market
share of 15-16 and almost now  I liked my life
ICC chief said in the back full group
that the management is very good what is there
till now in my voice mail playlist but
whenever I will read  I was right on
nov29 of will have to interest only
a plumber star helper job you are he is
working hard in the market because
where can I find insurance mediclaim
good law minute letter they are doing
good work for their sector at that time we will
see it but we need complete general insurance
so right we were living in Noida Sector-24 so
after coming I will have to think about it
but I have another question
today indigo video is old indigo
paint
that it would tech I could not make it did not make it there is
no vomit in my mind my
priority was second but
why is there not many
provider in
ours we are already
investing in
a new VIP back lid there is a child in front of the stomach
let the child be good then we will invest in quality I have
also used in edit I have
a child for years I have an IPO
came good quality dairy company has investors
support investing in indigo it is
very good for you as compared to them so
why nothing and the return on
equity is nothing it is this
All is well in the late stage,
keep your selection criteria firm, do
n't run after everyone, right Jai Kishan has
taken that these companies can be good, I
like to do some to-do, I have done
internship, nice presentation,
Niketan Bike Advice from Surat,
Doctor Jain broadcasters are great, Tarun
Sharma has studied very well, if you
remember lots of annual reports, he
gives you cheques, Doctor Web has given you all this,
he knows
how many annual reports you will search for to postpone it,
wonderful, wonderful Dilip Patel ji, live without you,
thank you Srinivas ji, Mr. Anwar
ji has written, I have to say that like
in Hindi, it was very nice that
you have completed it in English,
Mr. Rakesh ji, thank you friend, thank you to you,
also Pankaj has liked the Brad Pitt level Surai
Invest, okay, at which level should I like and
Chief Tarun Bank
officials are on leave, if we put them
in Ajmer Mandi, then the mistake is the horse in the fast, it will take
half, so A was the
pickup brother label sir,
but Uri metal call me to the 100
or  After that once we have done this completely
in this rally there is no time
for peace
that Ravan ji episode 84
loot 7722 ok Harvinder is chicken he is the
leader of the chapter note project should have in mind while
investing in him
for bleeding give winners will right side
absolutely size 30 no problem no worry
ki baat ko
khol di city's new hold for twenty
twenty years to man brother let me come with a very this
point he says such
tilak bade like and such situation rice
I can fold these three companies for 10-20 years
yes definitely we can do it but
emergently we can do it but he is
working in the insurance sector so we
can reduce here quickly that is a good
use and quality of life is for better
because when Bigg Boss saw him he got
angry so we can do it here
but we can keep it low
refer to Lutiya Sangh is
torch light or so that you very much sister  Ji
told absolutely right IS Selected Live,
you should invest in these two Vinod, such a biography
Rockstar Implementation Vinod ji
is waiting for you in your presentation, so thank
you sir, thank you, I have to say student,
positive member for telling, thank
you, thank you, Google profit, this hundred percent
vote percent, it was very good to subscribe to yesterday news channel,
which is the first company,
who is the leader, Divi's Lab, see in this sector,
as Shami told you, Sun Pharma, this latter does
not have that much quality,
so I have to go to a small company, De
Villiers cannot come in front of a high quality, long good company, I
told you that it can
definitely be made, Tarun ji told that a
completely rock company like TCS, Arvind ji
said that do honey and shoes, this is the first pretty pretty
chief company, you can hold on, one and a half
inch very mosted, romantic Milan Bhai,
so whom will we wait for tomorrow
and our cancer boxer Ashok
Sonagar ji who will be presenting on Havells and ATS
ad  Partha ji will give a
presentation on ad management from the state,
macro company is important, amazing sir,
NTSB, this is it, it is very much in a dream,
everyone is doing this incident sir and this is
David Management in Rang whose future is bright,
so all these three companies are very very important,
eager for the portfolio,
tomorrow's presentation will be more important, all
characters 16, balle-balle to everyone, now all
three have made
me proud today, thank you very much and
everyone and Jai Ho,
a time to sanction order